AMANDA FOX

Business Professional

SUMMARY

Self-motivated business professional with 6 years of experience in hyper-competitive market environments. Looking to bring my skills and integrity to a tech company with global reach where I can continue to embrace new concepts that better myself, my company and my customer's experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Representative at Cintas | Houston, TX

October 2018 — Present

- Consistent track record of exceeding goals by 10-20% and receiving quarterly performance bonuses.
- Technology Champion responsible for the technical training and development of sales team in areas including Microsoft Dynamics 365, Dynamics Connect, Sharepoint, Microsoft 365 services, Surface device, presentation tools and more.
- Active mentor to Sales Representatives and Management Trainees.
- Drive new and existing business sales by owning full sales cycle including prospecting, leading persuasive presentations, creating proposals, negotiating contracts, closing new accounts, managing implementation and ongoing account management.
- Work closely with service teams to exceed customer expectations, resulting in an annual retention rate of 97%.
- Collaborate with Technology Champions across organization to define, measure, and improve business processes, while recognizing and documenting tangible results.
- Maintain up-to-date industry and product knowledge to build credibility and value.

Software Engineer at 100Devs | Remote

May 2022 — Present

- Work with languages such as JavaScript, SQL, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Collaborate with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices.
- Build semantically structured web applications.

Recent Projects: SpaceCity StarGazers Web App with NASA API integration, Mix With Us Web App with Cocktail DB API integration, Makeup Designs by Lana Web App, and more.

Management Trainee at Cintas | Houston, TX

January 2017 — October 2018

- Grew assigned territory by 106%, ranked in the top 5% of the company.
- Led and managed sales team of 3.
- Managed projects as Product Champion overseeing new product launches, implementation and deadlines.
- Researched and prepared presentations for C-level executives regarding industry trends, competitor analysis, profitability reports, and internal operating inefficiencies.
- Conducted data analysis on product performance, identified areas of improvement, presented incentive programs resulting in 20% product growth.

CONTACT

832.654.5237

amandafox022@gmail.com

amandafox.dev

github.com/amandxfox

linkedin.com/in/amanda-fox-afox

AWARDS

Rookie of the Year

Winner's Circle

8x Summit Club

9x Pinnacle Club

5x Sales Monster

450K Club

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Dynamics 365

Microsoft 365

SAP

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

SQL

UI/UX

CERTIFICATION

Six Sigma Green Belt

EDUCATION

SFA State University

2012 - 2016

Degree: BBA General Business

Activities: 4-Year D1 Soccer

Scholarship Recipient